AARON BOOTH

Phone: (704) 962-9817 • Email: abooth 9422 @gmail.com • Charlotte, NC 28227 Github: https://github.com/ABooth9422 • Portfolio: https://abooth9422.github.io/ LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/abooth9422/

SUMMARY

Full-Stack Web Developer with over a decade of experience in Retail Management and a dedication to learning new technologies. Effective at combining creativity and creative problem solving to develop user-friendly applications. Known among staff and peers for strong determination and attention to detail when executing projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ¡Query, Bootstrap, React.js, Node.js, C#, .Net, Database Theory, Bookshelf.js, MongoDB, MySQL, Command Line, and Git

PROJECTS

Tattoo4U | Github: github.com/ABooth9422/Project1 | Site: abooth9422.github.io/Project1 Full Stack Developer Tattoo4U is an application that is designed to connect users with design styles in surrounding tattoos shops.

- Worked in a group of four creating JavaScript for the API call and the front-end development.
- Technologies and skills used: CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, Mapquest API, Yelp API, Google Firebase

GameScraper | Github: github.com/ABooth9422/scraper | Site: GameScraper Full Stack Developer Game Scraper is a full-stack application designed to scrape web-pages for top gaming articles.

- This was an individual project to make a full-stack application hosted by heroku.
- Technologies and skills used: CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Cheerio, Mongoob, Mongoose, Handlebars

EXPERIENCE

Technical Support / Hardware Installer

March 2019 - Present

Netsafe Solutions

Charlotte, NC

Daily responsibilities are to ensure that all customers' networks are operational if stationed at the help desk.

Key Accomplishments:

- Increased sales by 20% with on-site installs.
- Top Customer satisfaction rating from customer tickets

Addition Experience

Assistant Store Leader April 2017 - March 2019

Petsmart RockHill, SC

General Manager May 2013 - April 2017

PartyCity Charlotte, NC

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: UNCC, Charlotte, NC

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery,

Bootstrap, Firebase, NodeJS, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, HandelbarsJS & ReactJS.